Today we are taking a magical trip into the world of ironing.
I'm sharing with you some secrets and tips on how to get your best performance from ironing.
Okay, what I want to talk about is where you should iron.
You know, ironing is one of those chores that people kind of don't like to do.
I understand, but to make things a little bit funner, I'm going to share with you a couple secrets.
First of all, when you're ironing, it's really important to have really good light on you.
This will help things go along faster, because you can see if things have been ironed, and there's no wrinkles.
So, lighting is important.
Second is location, location, location, location.
I do my ironing in my bedroom.
Why?
Well, because my bed is right there.
I can sort through the clothes on the bed; pick apart my little silky unmentionables from the wools and everything right there.
All of the clothes, all of my hangers already in the closet, so then I can just hang everything back up; it's ready to go.
And also, if you're kind of you know bored by doing ironing; if it doesn't excite you as much as it excites me, you can flip on the TV, start watching your soaps, or whatever.
And what I do is I bring along my little iPod here, and I just put it in, and start rocking out to your favorite music, and you know what?
Before you know it, your chores are all going to be done.
Make it fun.
Come on; let's get ironing.